peach I always wanted a peach tree
I love peaches
I guess the climate in the locations where I've been
I guess a peach tree
wouldn't do so well
there's this one that I want named the miracle fruit
I'd love to acquire one of those plants
I feel like
we all have one or a few plants
that we always wanted
but for some reason
we can't get it
lemon balm that I currently have this
this was one of them that I felt that way about
ever since I rub the leaf and smell it
I always said I need one of those plants
now I have lemon balm and there are few other plants
this grape
this is a purple grape
so this is one of them
that I've always wanted
I managed to grow this from cuttings
right and now it's flourishing
I've acquired a few that I've always wanted
and I feel compelled to
to multiply them
and share them
with the farming and gardening community
so tell me
what's one plant you've always wanted
but for one reason or the other
you haven't gotten
a chance to get your hands on it yet
haven't gotten a chance to add it to your collection
give me your answer
because
your answer will help shape the plant catalogue
for future giveaways
for each giveaway
we choose 100 of the most enthusiastic home gardeners
for them to get plants that need forever homes
homes into the hands of people who
are actually willing
to take care of them